quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "1. What type of triangle has all three sides the same length?",
        "choices": ["Scalene","Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Equilateral"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. What type of triangle has two sides that are the same length and one side that is different?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Isosceles"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Which triangle has all sides of different lengths?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Scalene"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. What type of triangle has a 90-degree angle?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Right-Angled"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Which type of triangle can also be called an equiangular triangle because all its angles are equal?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Equilateral"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. If a triangle has one right angle, what type of triangle is it?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Right-Angled"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. What type of triangle is this if it has two equal sides and one angle that is not 90 degrees?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Isosceles"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. A triangle has sides of 3 cm, 4 cm, and 6 cm. What type of triangle is it?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Scalene"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Which type of triangle always has angles that add up to 180 degrees?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "All triangles"],
        "answer": "All triangles"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. Which type of triangle can never have an angle that is 90 degrees?",
        "choices": ["Scalene", "Right-Angled", "Isosceles", "Equilateral"],
        "answer": "Equilateral"
    }
]